

#### **Contacts**

Pilsen, Czech Republic +420 736 746 211 (CR) +380 994 091 743 (UA) malyk.vitaliy@gmail.com Telegram GitHub LinkedIn

#### **Tech skills**

- HTML5/CSS3
- Responsive/Adaptive design
- JavaScript
- Git/GITHub
- Parcel
- Webpack
- REST APIs
- React
- Redux Toolkit
- TypeScript
- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- Canva
- Figma
- AutoCAD

#### Soft skills

- Operations management
- Staff development
- Negotiation
- Critical thinking
- Team work
- Analytics skills

## Languages

- Ukrainian Native
- Czech Intermediate
- English Pre-Intermediate
- Russian Native

# Vitalii Malyk

## Junior frontend developer

#### Summary

As a junior front-end developer, I have a solid skill set covering HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React, and a solid understanding of back-end technologies such as Node.js and Express.js. My experience extends to using Agile/Scrum methodologies, ensuring efficient delivery of projects within set deadlines and budget constraints, while prioritizing improving the user experience. My passion for programming is fueled by the prospect of making a positive difference in both personal and business endeavors.

# **Project experience**

<u>PowerPulse</u>, <u>Link front</u>, <u>Link back</u>, [React, Redux-Toolkit, JS, CSS, Node.js, Express.js, TypeScript]

Adaptive application. Position: full stack developer. Pet projects.

<u>Phonebook</u>, <u>Link</u> [React, Redux Toolkit, JS, CSS] Adaptive application. Position: developer. I created the project using React and the Redux Toolkit.

Film library, Link [React, JS, CSS, HTML5]

Adaptive application. Position: developer. I created a project using React and and hooks.

TastyTreats, Link [HTML, CSS, JS]

Adaptive site layout on vanilla JavaScript. Position: developer.

Wristwatch, Link [HTML, CSS, JS]

Adaptive site layout. Position: Scrum Master, developer. A team project on GitHub Pages.

## Work experience

LLC "BudInvest", Ukraine (oct 2016 - feb 2022) Deputy General Director for Construction

- Conclusion of construction contracts
- Organization of the work of the construction department of the company
- Checking the budget documentation

LLC "DISK", Ukraine (feb 2013 - sep 2016)

Civil engineer - Department head

- Construction calculations
- Calculation of the cost of work
- Organization of construction

#### **Education**

2023

IT School GoIT

Full Stack Developer

2005 - 2010

Donbas Academy of Construction and Architecture

Civil engineer

